New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- NYCAP Publications - Other, 1981-2002; 6; 16.33 cubic ft.
  - Subseries 1: NYCAP Publications, Undated; 6.1
    - Common Sense Pest Control Quarterly, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - Common Sense Pest Control Quarterly, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Common Sense Pest Control Quarterly, 1994-1997 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Common Sense Pest Control Quarterly, 1997-2000 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - Common Sense Pest Control Quarterly, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Communicator, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - Community and Rural Development Institute Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Community and Rural Development Institute (CaRDI) News, 1993-1999 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - Community Connections/The Minnesota Project, 1992-2001 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - Community Development Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - Community Food Security News, 1995-1999 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - Community Ink, 1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Community Plume Newsletter, 1989 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - Components, University of California Agriculture Newsletter, 1990; 1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Connecticut Fund for the Environment Newsletter, 1986-1991 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - Controlling Interest, 1993 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Agriculture News Releases, Undated (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension, New York State Ornamentals Project Reports Relating to IPM, 1998-2002 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18-19)
    - Cornell University Agriculture and Life Sciences News, 1991; 1994 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - Corporate Hog Update, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - The Cultivar, 1986-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - Current Research Monitor, Pesticide Action Network UK/ The Pesticide Trust, 1993-2002 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - Current The Journal of North Country Action, 1989-1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - Cycle, Environmental Action Coalition Newsletter, 1992-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
    - The Delicate Balance/The National Center for Environmental Health Strategies, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - The Delicate Balance/The National Center for Environmental Health Strategies, 1994 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - The Disability Rag, 1996 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - Disable in Action Activist, 1996 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - Discernment is Needed, Share, Care, and Prayer, 1998 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - Down to Earth Newsletter, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)
    - E-Law (Environmental Law Alliance Worldwide) Newsletter, 1992-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 32)
    - Eagle's Eye, Bethlehem Central School Newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 33)
    - Earth First, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 34)
    - Earth Island Journal, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 35)
    - Earth Island Journal, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 36)
    - Earth Times, Spring and Summer, 1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 37)
    - Earth Roots, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 38)
    - Earth Keeping, 1989 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 39)
    - The ECHO/ Ecological Health Organization, 1992-2000 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 40)
    - Eco Justice Quarterly, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 41)
    - Ecolife, Information and Support for Persons with Chemical Sensitivities, 1993-1997 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 42)
    - Ecologic News, 1995 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 43)
    - Ecological Agriculture Projects News, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 44)
    - Ecological Health Organization and Action Coalition Newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 45)
    - Ecology and Environment Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1990-1992; 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - Ecology Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Ecomedia Bulletin: Toronto's Anarchist Bi-Weekly, Issue #36, 1988 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - The Egg: A Journal of Eco-Justice, 1988-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - The Egg: A Journal of Eco-Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - E.I. Circle of Prayer, Share, Care and Prayer, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - The Elm Advisor, 1991-1993 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Environ Magazine, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - Environment Bulletin, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Access Research Network Newsletter, 1991 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - Environmental Advocates (EPL) Voters' Guides, 1994; 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Business Association of New York Newsletter, 1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady News, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - Environmental Compliance and Litigation Strategy News, 1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Environmental Health Monthly, 1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - Environmental Health Monthly, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - Environmental Health Monthly, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - Environmental Health Monthly, 1997 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18)
    - Environmental Health Perspectives, 2001 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 19)
    - The Environmental Illness Network, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - Environmental News, Palouse-Clearwater Environmental Institute, Volume 3, #4, 1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - The Environmental Physician, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - Environmental Politics Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - The Environmental Wellness Network, 1995 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - Environmental Wellness Network, 1999 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
    - Environmental Science and Technology, 2002 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - Environmentally Friendly, 1999 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - Environmentally Ill (EI) Home Companion, 1995 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - Environmentarian, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - ENYCOSH News, 1989-1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - EPA Food Quality Protection Act, 1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1988-1991 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 32)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 33)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1993 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 34)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 35)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 2000-2002 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 36)
    - Facets of Freshwater, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 37)
    - Facets of Freshwater, 1993-1995 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 38)
    - Facts to Act On/Institute for Local Self-Reliance, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 39)
    - Farm Chemicals, 1990 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 40)
    - Farmer to Farmer: California Farming at Its Best, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 41)
    - Farmer to Farmer/Ozark Small Farm Viability Project, 1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 42)
    - Farming Alternatives, 2000 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 43)
    - Farming and Organic Food Newsletters, miscellaneous, 1985; 1989; 1990; 1995-1996; 1999-2000 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 44)
    - Farmland Update, 1994 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 45)
    - Farmworker Justice News, 1990-2000 (Box 4 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 46)
    - Felix Letter, A Commentary on Nutrition, 1992; 1995; Undated (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - Focus Nonprofit, Council of Community Services of New York State, 1996 Spring (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Focus on Pesticides, 1997-1999 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Foghorn, 1990; 1992 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - Food and Water Journal, 1996 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Food First Backgrounder, 1995-2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - Food First News and Views, 1985-2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Food First Nutrition Group Annual Report and Handouts, 1987 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - Forest and Land Planning Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1988; 1990; 1992-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - FPANA Reports, 1994 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - From the Ground Up, 1998-2002 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - From the Ground Up, 2002 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Friends of the Earth, 1993-1995 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - From the Ground Up, Michigan Environmental News, 1998-2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Fumigants and Pheromones, 1995 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - The Fund For Animals, 1999 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - The Furrow, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - FYI: A Health and Safety Newsletter for Office Workers, 1990-2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18)
    - GASP: Newsletter of the Rhode Island Group for Alternatives to Spraying Pesticides, 1988-1994 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 19)
    - Gempler's IPM Solutions, 2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - The Gene Exchange, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - The Gene Exchange, 1993-1997 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - Generation Green, Evanston, Illinois, Annual Report, 2002 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - Gene Watch, 1985 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - Gene Watch, 1999-2002 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
    - GEO Newsletter, 2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - The Germinator, 2001-2002 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - Glacial Erratic: The Evolutionary Environmental Journal, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - Global Pesticide Campaigner, 1990-1994 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - Global Pesticide Campaigner, 1994-1997 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - Global Pesticide Campaigner, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)
    - Global Pesticide Campaigner, 1998-2001 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 32)
    - Global Pesticide Campaigner, 2001-2004 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 33)
    - Global Pesticide Monitor, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 34)
    - Grapevine/Center for Environmental Education Newsletter, 1997-1999 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 35)
    - Grassroots Economic Organizing Newsletter, 1992-1996 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 36)
    - Grassroots Economic Organizing Newsletter, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 37)
    - Grassroots Environmental Organization, GREO Newsletter, 1993 March (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 38)
    - Grassroots: The Voice of the New York Farm Bureau, 1991 November (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 39)
    - Great Lakes United, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 40)
    - Great Lakes United, 1993-1996 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 41)
    - The Green Drummer, 1993-1995 (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 42)
    - Green Alternatives for Health and the Environment, Undated (Box 5 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 43)
    - The Green Guide, 1994-2002 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - Green Overgrow the Government Times, 1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Greener Roadsides, 1999 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Green Teacher, 1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - The Green Drummer, May-June, 1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Green Keeping, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - Grower, 1993-1994 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Grower, 1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - The Harmony Hill Companion, 1998 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - The Harvest Times, 1994 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - Hazards Networker Document Bulletin, 1993; Undated (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Substances and Public Health, 1996 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Hazards, 1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - The Healer- Central New York HEAL, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Health and Healing Wisdom Journal, 2002 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - Health and Safety News, 1990-1997 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - Health Facts/Center for Medical Consumers, 1993-1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - The Health Resource Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18)
    - Healthwatch, 1994 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 19)
    - Healthworks, Central New York Council on Occupational Safety and Health, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - Healthy Home and Workplace, 1990-1994 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - Healthy Horizons, 1998-2001 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - Healthy School Environment Report, 1998 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - H.E.I.R.S. Clean Living Resources, 1999 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - Henry A. Wallace Institute for Alternative Agriculture, 1993 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
      Annual Report, 1994, undated.
    - Home Grown Green, Resources for Environment/Health, 1994 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - Honey Bee, Indian Institute of Management, 1992; 2000 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - Hort Ideas, 1986-1988 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - Hort Ideas, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - Hort Ideas, 1991 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - Hort Ideas, 1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)
    - Hort Ideas, 1993 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 32)
    - Hort Ideas, 1994-1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 33)
    - Hort Ideas, 1996-1997 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 34)
    - Hort Ideas, 1998-2003 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 35)
    - HSUS News, The Humane Society of the United States, 1992 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 36)
    - Hudson Valley Green Times, 1991; 1993-1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 37)
    - Hudson Valley Green Times, 1995-2000 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 38)
    - The Human Ecologist, 1993-1995 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 39)
    - The Human Ecologist, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 40)
    - The Human Ecologist, 1997-1999 (Box 6 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 41)
    - The Human Ecologist, 1999-2000 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - The Human Ecologist, 2001-2002 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Human Ecology Action League of Central New York, Health Briefs, 1997 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Human Ecology Action League (HEAL) New York City, Chapter Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - Human Ecology Action League Rochester Newsletter, 1989; 1992 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Human Ecology Resources, 1996 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - The Human Ecology Study Group, 1997-2002 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Huxley Institute for Biosocial Research Publications, 1991-1993 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - I Am Jeremiah, 2001 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - ICET News, Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology at Cornell University, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - IL Pesticide Education News, 1996 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - Inner Voice, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Innovations in Sustainable Agriculture, 1993-1995 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - Inquiry in Action, 1998 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Institute for Alternative Agriculture, Annual Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - Intervenor: The Newsletter of the Canadian Environmental Law Association, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - Intervenor: The Newsletter of the Canadian Environmental Law Association, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - Intervenor: The Newsletter of the Canadian Environmental Law Association, 1995-1997 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18)
    - Iowa State University Sustainable Agriculture, 1990 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 19)
    - The IPM Great Lakes, 1997 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - The IPM in Schools, 1996 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - The IPM Laboratories Quarterly, 1988-1993 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - The IPM Monitor, 1995 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - The IPM News Northeast, 2001 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1979-1982 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1982-1984 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1984-1986 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1986-1987 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1988-1989 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1989-1990 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 32)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1993-1996 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 33)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1996-1997 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 34)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1997-1998 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 35)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1998-1999 (Box 7 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 36)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 1999-2001 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 2001-2002 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - The IPM Practitioner, 2002-2004 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Iroquois Environmental Newsletter, 1993-2002 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - Japan Occupational Safety and Health Resource Center Newsletter, 1998 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1990 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1991 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1992 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 8)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1993 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 9)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1994-1996 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 10)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1997-2002 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 11)
    - Just Food Bulletin, 1996 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 12)
    - Just Food News, 2001 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 13)
    - Knolls Action Project/Social Justice Center, Newsletter, 1993 August (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 14)
    - Labor and Environment News, from the NYC Labor and Environment Network, 1995 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 15)
    - Labor-Community Reporter, 1990; 1994-1995 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 16)
    - Labor Notes, 1988-1992 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 17)
    - Lake Ontario Health and Environment Directory, 1991 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 18)
    - The Land Institute Annual Report, 1991 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 19)
    - The Land Report/The Land Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 20)
    - The Land Report/The Land Institute, 1993-1995 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 21)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 22)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, 1993-1994 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 23)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 24)
    - LEAF Briefs, Legal Environmental Assistance Foundation, 1990-1995 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 25)
    - LEAN News, Louisiana Environmental Action Network, 1993 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 26)
    - Leopold Center for Sustainable Agriculture, Progress Report, 1997; 2002 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 27)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, 1991-1992 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 28)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, 1993-1995 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 29)
    - Littorally Speaking, 1994 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 30)
    - Local 99, Drugs, Hospital, and Health Care Workers News, 1990 (Box 8 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 31)